Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
- Additions (2010-0071 and 2010-0107) 1966-2009, (5 boxes)
  - Bill Black's Fun Comics, Issue 3
Marksman, The, Hero/Heroic [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 415
Mars, First [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 398
Marshal Law, Epic [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 389
Martha Washington, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 348, 349
Martian Manhunter, DC [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s, 2000s ] Box: 80, 82, 126, 138, 157, 167, 168
Marvel Action Hour, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 194, 206, 224, 228
Marvel Boy, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 237, 242, 247, 258
Marvel Chillers, Marvel [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 179, 189, 292
Marvel Classics Comics Series, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 188
Marvel Collectors Item Classics, Marvel [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 179
Marvel Comics Presents, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 194, 202, 206, 212, 218, 224, 228, 234, 249, 252, 297, 302
Marvel Comics Super Special, A, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 460
Marvel Double Feature, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 218, 224, 228
Marvel Family, The, Fawcett [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 394
Marvel Fanfare, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 194, 202, 206, 212, 234, 247, 252, 258, 264, 276, 288, 297, 300
Marvel Feature, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 180, 186, 264
Marvel Graphic Novel: Ka-zar; the Guns of the Savage Land, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 460
Marvel Graphic Novel: The Pit, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 252
Marvel Heroes & Legends, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 202, 228
Marvel Holiday Special, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 202, 212, 218, 224, 228
Marvel Knights, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 237, 242, 247, 258, 305
Marvel Mangaverse, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 252
Marvel Masterpieces Collection, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 218, 224, 228
Marvel Mystery Comics, Marvel [Issues from: 1940s, 1990s ] Box: 242, 292
Marvel No-Prize Book, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 281
Marvel Premiere, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s ] Box: 281
Marvel Presents, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 180
Marvel Saga: Official History of Marvel Universe, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 247, 252, 258, 288, 297, 300
Marvel Spotlight, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s ] Box: 264, 281
Marvel Super Heroes Secret Wars, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 280, 288
Marvel Super Special, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 460
Marvel Super-Heroes, Marvel [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s, 1990s ] Box: 182, 194, 202, 206, 212, 218, 224, 228, 247
Marvel Tails starring Peter Porker, the Spectacular Spider-Ham, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 276
Marvel Tales, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Marvel Tales, Marvel [Issues from: 1940s, 1950s, 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 179, 292, 307
Marvel Team-Up, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 202, 212, 228, 234, 265, 271, 282, 288
Marvel Two-in-One, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s ] Box: 188, 271, 272
Marvel Universe, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 202, 228, 242
Marvel Valentine Special, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 212
Marvel versus DC/DC versus Marvel, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 202
Marvel X-Men Collection, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 226
Marvel: 1990 The Year in Review, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 460
Marvel: 1991 The Year in Review, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 460
Marvel: Shadow & Light, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 212
Marvel: The Lost Generation, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 237, 242, 247, 258
Marvels Comics, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 242
Marvel's Greatest Comics, Marvel [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 179, 186
Marvels, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 194, 202, 206, 218, 224
Mary Marvel, Fawcett [Issues from: 1940s ] Box: 394
Mary Roberts Rinehart's The Bat, Adventure Comics [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 325
Mask of Zorro, The, Dell [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 360
Mask of Zorro, The, Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
Mask, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 111, 129, 146, 162
Masked Man, The, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 384
Masked Raider, Charlton [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s ] Box: 338
Master of Kung Fu, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 212, 265, 266, 280, 282
Masters of the Universe, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 83
Masters of the Universe, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 247, 252, 258, 297
Masterworks Series of Great Comic Book Artists, The, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 104
Matt Champion, Metro [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 431
Matt Slade, Gunfighter, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Maverick, Dell [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s ] Box: 360
Maverick, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 203, 215, 227, 235
Max Brand's Silvertip, Dell [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 360
Maximum Security, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 242, 258
Maxx, The, Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
Maze Agency, The, Caliber [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 334
Maze Agency, The, Comico [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 342
Maze Agency, The, Innovation [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 423
'Mazing Man, DC [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 52, 129, 146, 162
MD, EC [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 381
Mean Bitch Thrills, Print Mint [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 452
Mecha Special, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 349
Mechanics, Fantagraphics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 393
Medal of Honor Special, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 349
Medusa Chain, The, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 455
Megaton Man, Kitchen Sink [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 424
Melvin Monster, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 360
Men in Action, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Men into Space, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
Men of War, DC [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s ] Box: 92, 111
Menace, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Mephisto vs..., Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 252, 297
Merlin, Adventure Comics [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 325
Merton of the Movement, Cocoanut Comix [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 450
Meta-4, First [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 398
Metal Men, DC [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s, 1990s ] Box: 49, 67, 85, 142, 153
Metamorpho, DC [Issues from: 1960s, 1990s ] Box: 49, 67, 142
Metropolis S.C.U., DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 66, 75
Mickey and Goofy Explore Energy Conservation, Disney [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 370
Mickey Mouse and Goofy Explore Energy, Disney [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 370
Mickey Mouse, Dell [Issues from: 1940s ] Box: 361
Mickey Mouse, Gold Key [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 408
Micronauts, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s ] Box: 272, 276, 282, 289, 297
Midnight Men, Epic [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 389
Midnight Mystery, ACG [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 323
Midnight Sons Unlimited, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 206, 218, 223, 228
Midnight Surfer Special, The, Quality [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 435
Midnight Tales, Charlton [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 338
Mighty Comics, Radio [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 436, 437
Mighty Crusaders, The, Archie Publications [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 327
Mighty Crusaders, The, Radio [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 437
Mighty Samson, Gold Key [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 408
Mighty Thor, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s, 1990s, 2000s ] Box: 194, 203, 206, 212, 218, 224, 231, 233, 245, 299, 304, 462
Millennium Editions, DC [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 135, 138, 157, 168, 176
Millennium Index, Independent Comics Group [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 423
Millennium, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 127, 162
Milton Caniff's Steve Canyon, Dell [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 361
Miracle Squad, The, Upshot Graphics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 440
Miracle Squad: Blood and Dust, The, Apple [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 326
Miracleman, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 384
Miss Fury, Adventure Comics [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 325
Mister E, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 44
Mister Ed, The Talking Horse, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
Mister Miracle, DC [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 44, 50, 67, 73, 82, 96, 127, 146, 162, 176
Mister X, Vortex [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 446
Misty, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 252, 289, 297, 300
Moby Dick, Dell [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 361
Modesty Blasé, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 60
Moebius O-The Horny Goof and Other Underground Stories, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 455
Moebius [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 469
Mom's Homemade Comics, Krupp Comic Works [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 450
Monkeyman & O'Brien, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 349
Monolith, Comico [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 343
Monolith, Last Gasp/Last Gasp-Eco Funnies [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 451
Monster Hunters, Charlton [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 338
Monster, Quality [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 435
Monsters on the Prowl, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 181
Moon Girl and the Prince, EC [Issues from: 1940s ] Box: 381
Moon Knight, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 218, 228, 234, 242, 258, 266, 276, 289
Moon Mullins, Dell [Issues from: 1930s ] Box: 361
Moon Mullins, Michel Publications [Issues from: 1940s ] Box: 431
Moondog, Print Mint [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 452
Moonshadow, Epic [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 389
Morbius: The Living Vampire, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 63
Morbius: The Living Vampire, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 194, 218, 224, 228
More Fun Comics, DC [Issues from: 1930s, 1940s ] Box: 109, 139, 176B, 454
More Secret Origins, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 170
Morlock 2001, Atlas [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 331
Morningstar Special, Comico [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 343
Mother's Oats Comix, Rip Off Press [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 453
Motor City Comics, Rip Off Press [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 453
Mr. District Attorney, DC [Issues from: 1940s, 1950s ] Box: 40, 87, 159
Mr. Monster, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 349
Mr. Monster, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 384
Mr. Mxyzptlk, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 75
Mr. Natural, Apex Novelties [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 450
Mr. Natural, Print Mint [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 452
Ms. Marvel, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 272, 282
Ms. Tree, Aardvark-Vanaheim [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 319
Ms. Tree, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 44, 50, 82, 176
Ms. Tree, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 384
Ms. Tree, Renegade [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 437
Mummy, The, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
Mummy, The, Monster [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 431
Munden's Bar, First [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 398
Muppet Babies, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 247, 253, 258, 282, 289, 297, 300
Murcielaga She-Bat, Hero/Heroic [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 415
Murder, Renegade [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 437
Mutant Misadventures of Cloak and Dagger, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 235, 249, 253, 302
Mutant X, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s, 2000s ] Box: 235, 238, 243, 249, 258
Mutants of the Metropolis, The Los Angeles Comic Book Company [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 451
Mutants, Epic [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 389
Muties, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 305
My Favorite Martian, Gold Key [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 408
My Greatest Adventure, DC [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 84, 139, 158
My Love, Marvel [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 188
My Name is Chaos, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 82
My Name is Holocaust, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 64
My Own Romance, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
My Romantic Adventures, ACG [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s ] Box: 323
Myron Moose Funnies, Myron Moose Comic Book Works [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 451
Mysteries of Unexplored Worlds, Charlton [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s ] Box: 338
Mysterious Suspense, Charlton [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 338
Mystery Comics Digest, Gold Key [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 464
Mystery in Space, DC [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s, 1980s ] Box: 7, 12, 40, 123, 124
Mystery Tales, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Mystery Tales, Super Comics [Issues from: [1960s] ] Box: 439
Mystic, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Mystical Tales, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Mystique and Sabretooth, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 204, 214
Myth Adventures, Apple/Warp [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 326
Myth Adventures, Warp [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 447, 468
Myth Conceptions, Apple/Warp [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 326
'Nam, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 194, 203, 206, 213, 218, 223, 234, 247, 253, 258, 297, 300
Namor, the Sub-Mariner, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 194, 203, 206, 213, 218, 223, 228, 234, 249
Nard N' Pat, Cartoonists' Co-op Press [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 450
Nathaniel Dusk, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 90, 102, 111, 129
National Comics, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 176
Navy Action, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Navy Combat, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Navy Tales, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Naza, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
Nazz, The, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 49, 80
Neil Gaiman's Mr. Hero-The Newmatic Man, Tekno [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 439
Neil the Horse Comics and Stories, Aardvark-Vanaheim [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 450
Nemesis the Warlock, Fleetway Quality [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 401
Nemesis the Warlock, Quality [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 435
Nemesis, Eagle [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 380
Netherworlds, Adventure Publications [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 326
Neutro, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
New Adventures of Charlie Chan, The, DC [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 32, 159
New Adventures of Jesus, The, Rip Off Press [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 453
New Adventures of Judo Joe, Ace Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 320
New America, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 384
New Crime Files of Michael Mauser Private Eye, The, Apple [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 326
New Defenders, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 289, 300
New DNAgents, The, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 384-385
New Eternals: Apocalypse Now, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 237
New Frontier, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 349
New Gods, DC [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 47, 57, 64, 74, 80, 96, 101, 103, 128, 146, 163, 176
New Guardians, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 128, 146, 163
New Heroic Comics, Famous Funnies [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 393
New Justice Machine Mini-Series, The, Innovation [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 423
New Legends, Boston Comicworks [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 450
New Men, Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
New Mutants, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 190, 214, 227, 235, 249, 253, 258, 276, 289, 302
New Shadowhawk, The, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 75
New ShadowHawk, The, Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
New Stateman, Fleetway Quality [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 401
New Talent Showcase, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 90
New Teen Titans, The, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 90, 94, 106, 131, 146, 163
New Titans, The, DC [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 44, 57, 61, 74, 86, 129, 146, 163, 176, 176B
New Two-Fisted Tales, The, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 349
New Warriors, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s, 2000s ] Box: 193, 203, 206, 212, 217, 224, 228, 234, 237, 242, 247
New Wave, The, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 385
New X-Men, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 244, 253, 258, 305
Newstime, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 455
Nexus, Capital [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 334, 455
Nexus, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 349
Nexus, First [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 398, 399
NFL Super Pro, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 212
Nick Fury Vs. S.H.I.E.L.D., Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 258, 297, 300
Nick Fury, Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D., Marvel [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s, 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 193, 203, 206, 213, 218, 234, 242, 247, 253, 282, 289, 297
Night and the Enemy, Comico [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 462
Night Force, DC [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 74, 82, 83, 176
Night Glider, Topps [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 439
Night Music, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 385
Night Nurse, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 180
Night Rider, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 188
Night Thrasher, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 193, 203, 224, 228
Nightcat, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 213
Nightcrawler, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 2000s ] Box: 253, 289, 302, 305
Nighthawk, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 242
Nightmare, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 206, 236
Nightmares, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 385
Nightmask, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 247, 253, 297
Nightraven, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 460
Nightstalkers, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 213, 224, 236
Nightwatch, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 206, 224, 236
Nightwing, DC [Issues from: 1990s, 2000s ] Box: 42, 43, 66, 71, 82, 134, 138, 146, 157,
1963..., Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
Ninja Elite, Adventure Publications [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 326
Ninjak, Valiant [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 443
Nocturne, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 206
Nomad, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 193, 213, 224, 236
Noman, Tower [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 440
Noof Unnies, Hell Comics [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 450
Normalman, Aardvark-Vanaheim [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 319
Normalman, Renegade [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 437
North to Alaska, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
Northstar, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 223
(Not Only) The Best of Wonder Warthog, Rip Off Press [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 453
(Not Only) The Best of Wonder Warthog, Volume III, Print Mint [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 452
Nova, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s, 1990s ] Box: 193, 203, 206, 223, 236, 247, 258, 282
Nth Man: The Ultimate Ninja, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 247, 253, 297
Nukla, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
O.G. Whiz, Gold Key [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 408
Obnoxio the Clown, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 282
Occult Files of Dr. Spektor, The, Gold Key [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 408
Official Buzz Sawyer, The, Pioneer [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 433
Official Crisis on Infinite Earths Crossover Index, The, Independent Comics Group [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 423
Official Crisis on Infinite Earths Index, The, Independent Comics Group [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 423
Official Doom Patrol Index, The, Independent Comics Group [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 423
Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 196, 203, 220, 224, 228, 234, 247, 253, 259, 276, 282, 297, 300
Official Hawkman Index, The, Independent Comics Group [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 423
Official Johnny Hazard, The, Pioneer [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 433
Official Jungle Jim, The, Pioneer [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 433
Official Justice League of America Index, The, Independent Comics Group [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 423
Official Legion of Super-Heroes, The, Independent Comics Group [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 423
Official Mandrake, The, Pioneer [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 433
Official Marvel Index to Amazing Spider-Man, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 289
Official Marvel Index to Avengers, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 253, 259, 295
Official Marvel Index to Fantastic Four, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 253, 289, 296, 300
Official Marvel Index to Marvel Team-Up, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 253, 289, 297, 300
Official Marvel Index to X-Men, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 217, 253, 259, 302
Official Modesty Blaise, The, Pioneer [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 433
Official Prince Valiant, The, Pioneer [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 433
Official Rip Kirby, The, Pioneer [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 433
Official Secret Agent, The, Pioneer [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 433
Official Teen Titans Index, The, Independent Comics Group [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 423
Oktoberfest Comics, Now and Then Publications [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 451
OMAC: One Man Army Corps, DC [Issues from: 1970s, 1990s ] Box: 82, 96
Omega Men, The, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 90, 107, 127, 163
Omega, the Unknown, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 289
On a Pale Horse, Innovation [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 423
On Stage, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
One Million Years Ago, St. John Publishing [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 438
One, The, Epic [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 389
Onslaught, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 203, 204, 214
Open Space, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 236, 247
Operation: Knightstrike, Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
Operation: Peril, ACG [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 323
Orbit, Eclipse Books [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 381
Order, The, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 305
Origin of Defiant Universe, The, Defiant [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 354
Original Black Cat, The, Lorne-Harvey Productions [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 427
Original Dick Tracy, The, Gladstone [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 403, 459
Original E-Man and Michael Mauser, The, First [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 399
Original Shield, The, Archie Publications [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 328
Original Swamp Thing Saga, DC [Issues from: 1970s, 1980s ] Box: 15, 98
Orion, DC [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 134, 138, 146, 157, 168, 176
Osborne Journals, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 209
Others, The, Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
Our Army at War, DC [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 20, 37, 87, 110, 113, 114, 121, 151, 152
Our Fighting Forces, DC [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 92, 111, 112, 117, 119
Our Gang Comics, Dell [Issues from: 1940s ] Box: 361
Our Love Story, Marvel [Issues from: 1960s, 1970s ] Box: 180
Out of the Night, ACG [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 323
Out of the Vortex, Dark Horse [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 349
Out Of This World, Charlton [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 339
Outcasts, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 131, 163
Outer Space, Charlton [Issues from: 1950s, 1960s ] Box: 339
Outlaw Kid, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Outlaw Kid, The, Marvel [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 307
Outlaw, DC [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 3
Outlaws of the West, Charlton [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 339
Outlaws, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 48, 86
Outsiders, DC [Issues from: 1980s, 1990s ] Box: 50, 61, 74, 90, 131, 146, 163
Over the Edge, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 203, 206
Owl, The, Gold Key [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 408
Owlhoots, Kitchen Sink [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 424
Oz-Wonderland Wars, The, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 90, 130
P. J. Warlock, Eclipse Comics [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 385
P.I.'s, The: Michael Mauser and Ms. Tree, First [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 399
Pact, The, Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
Paradise X, Marvel [Issues from: 2000s ] Box: 253, 305
Parallax, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 63
Paranoia, Adventure Comics [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 325
Parsifal, Star*Reach Productions [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 453
Pat Savage: The Woman of Bronze Family Blood Special, Millenium [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 431
Patsy and Hedy, Atlas [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 331
Peacemaker, DC [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 129, 163
Peacemaker, The, Charlton [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 339
Pendragon, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 193, 218
People's Comics, The, Golden Gate Publishing [Issues from: 1970s ] Box: 450
Pep, Archie Publications [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 328
Perfect Love, Ziff-Davis [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 449
Peter Cannon, Thunderbolt, DC [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 48, 55, 63, 86
Peter Gunn, Dell [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 361
Peter Pan: The Return to Never-Never Land, Adventure Comics [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 325
Peter Parker, The Spectacular Spider-Man, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 248, 253, 259, 272, 276, 289, 301
Peter Parker: Spider-Man, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s, 2000s ] Box: 236, 238, 239, 248, 253, 259, 305
Peter Parker: Spider-Man/Elektra '98, Marvel [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 239
Peter Porker, the Spectacular Spider-Ham, Marvel [Issues from: 1980s ] Box: 248, 253, 290, 301
Petunia, Dell [Issues from: 1950s ] Box: 361
Phantom Blot, The, Gold Key [Issues from: 1960s ] Box: 409
Phantom Force, Genesis West [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 401
Phantom Force, Image [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 418
Phantom Limited Series, Pioneer [Issues from: 1990s ] Box: 434